

# **PRINCE RUSWA**

DIGITAL MARKETER

## CONTACT

- £ +263 78 627 4798
- princeruswa46@gmail.com
- ☐ Prince Ruswa
- P Harare, Zimbabwe

#### **EDUCATION**

Ordinary Level Excellent College 2013 - 2017

Digital Markerting Uncommon.Org 2022 - 2023

## **EXPERTISE**

Digital Marketing

SMM

Copywriting

SEO

# LANGUAGE

English

Shona

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a passionate digital marketer with a proven track record of driving online brand presence, increasing website traffic, and optimizing conversion rates. Experienced in developing and executing comprehensive digital marketing strategies across multiple channels, including social media, search engine optimization (SEO), pay-per-click (PPC) advertising, email marketing, and content marketing.

## **EXPERIENCE**

O January 2021 BJP Petrolium

#### **Fuel Attendent**

Fuel Attendant with extensive experience delivering exceptional customer service and ensuring smooth operations at fuel stations. Proficient in handling fuel pumps, managing fuel transactions, and providing accurate and efficient fueling services to customers. Strong interpersonal skills with a focus on customer satisfaction, resolving customer concerns, and fostering positive relationships. Proactive and reliable team player, capable of working efficiently in fast-paced environments while upholding high standards of professionalism.

2017 - 2019

Civil Aviation Authority Of Zimbabwe

#### Auditor

Prepared detailed audit reports summarising findings, recommendations, and areas of improvement for management and stakeholders.

Risk Assessment and Management:Conducted risk assessments to identify potential areas of vulnerability and assessed the adequacy of internal controls.

Developed risk mitigation strategies, implemented control enhancements, and monitored their effectiveness.

2022 - 2023

Uncommon.Org

## Youth Coding

I am currently taking part in a youth coding program that focuses on teaching primary and secondary school students how to code and develop impressive games in our community.

# REFERENCE

## Rachel

Digital Marketer, Uncommon.Org

Phone: +263 77 385 8750 Email: racheal@uncommon.org

# Timorthy

Digital Marketer, Uncommon.Org

Phone: +263 78 289 6119 Email: timothy@uncommon.org